Guide to the Sue M. Durrant Papers 1956-2006
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Office files, 1956-2006
  - WSU Women's Basketball, 1975-1981
    - JoBe Smith, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 353)
    - Debbie Reser, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 354)
    - Carrie (Carolyn Marilyn) Reiner, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 355)
    - Katy Thorne, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 356)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 357)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and articles, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 358)
    - Administration, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 359)
    - Score Table, 1977-1981 (Box 19, Folder 360)
    - Academic Coordinator Admissions, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 361)
    - JV Basketball travel information, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 362)
    - Correspondence and mailing lists, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 363)
    - Miscellaneous, including pamphlets, 1975-1990 (Box 19, Folder 364)
    - Contributed Funds, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 365)
    - Fundraising, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 366)
    - Managers and reports, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 367)
    - Media, Captains, Scorer, 30-second clock, Timer, Schedule Cards, Sports Information, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 368)
    - Parade Magazine All-American selections, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 369)
    - The Challenge- Women’s Athletics Newsletter 1979 (Box 20, Folder 370)
    - Summer addresses, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 371)
    - Basketball organizational meeting, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 372)
    - Travel documents, contracts, itineraries, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 373)
    - Travel documents, contracts, itineraries; 1976-1977, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 374)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 375)
    - Assistant Coach Search, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 376)
    - Practice schedules and outlines, 1978-1982 (Box 20, Folder 377-384)
    - Practice schedules and outlines, 1978-1982 (continued) (Box 21, Folder 385-387)
  - WSU Women's Athletics Coaches Handbook, Basketball, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 388-390)
  - Sport Management
    - Sport Management 290 Lab activities and requirements, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 391-392)
    - Internship Articles, Intern Manual, miscellaneous; undated (Box 21, Folder 393)
    - Sport Management 488, article: "What They Don't Teach You at Harvard Business School" by Mark. H. McCormack (Box 21, Folder 394)
    - Majors, advising 1985-1989; photograph, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 395)
    - Alumni newsletters, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 396)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 397)
    - Internship Manual Draft, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 398)
    - Position and rationale, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 399)
    - Sport Management committee, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 400)
  - College of Education, Faculty Affairs Committee, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 401)
  - College of Education, ad hoc committee (Pre College of Education Faculty Affairs Committee), 1987 (Box 22, Folder 404)
  - Physical Education Sports and Leisure Studies (PESLS), 1980s (Box 22, Folder 405)
  - PESLS Major Advising and Options forms (Box 22, Folder 406)
  - Coaching Minor Program, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 407)
  - PESLS majors, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 408)
  - PESLS faculty meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 409-410)
  - PESLS, department committee information, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 411)
  - Work Equalization supplemental, overheads; 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 412)
  - Work Equalization, ad hoc committee, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 413-415)
  - PESLS
    - University census information, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 416)
    - Faculty Meetings, follow up on department merger; 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 417)
    - Merger process, Physical Education, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 418)
    - Delphi Procedures Strategic Planning Committee, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 419-421)
    - Physical Education merger, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 422)
    - Cougar Swim Lessons, undated (Box 23, Folder 423-424)
  - WSU Intramural Sports Program Standard Operating Procedure Manual, undated (Box 23, Folder 425)
  - Department of Physical Education for Women, Standard Operating Procedure Manual, Carol E. Gordon, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 426-428)
- Series 2: Audio Recordings and Memorabilia
  - Fish Fans Group Aquatic Choreography, audio recording (reel to reel), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 429)
  - Jesse Welch seminar audiocassette, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 430-435)
  - Edward Leader Effective Recruiting Seminar audiocassette, "Remembering Everyone's Name," 1979 (Box 24, Folder 436)
  - George Raveling seminar audiocassette, "The Home Visit," 1982 (Box 24, Folder 437-438)
  - Bobo Brayton seminar audiocassette, "Recruiting In-State with a Limited Budget," 1983 (Box 24, Folder 439)
  - Plaque commemorating Republic of China vs. WSU Women's Basketball, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 441)